Guide to the Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015.
Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015
- Series I. Administrative Files
  - Executive Staff
    - Elizabeth Birch, 1994-2004
      - After Stonewall, 1998-2000 (Box 98, Folder 60)
      - Alignment Strategies, Inc: Diversity Initiative, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 61)
      - American Airlines GLEAM, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 62)
      - Ellerbe Becket, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 63)
      - BOD Exec. C'ee Conference Call, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 64)
      - Equality at HM, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 65)
      - Equality Rocks Conference Call, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 66)
      - Federation, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 67)
      - Gore Correspondence, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 68)
      - Iowa 2000 Presidential Caucus Project, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 69)
      - Keppler Associates, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 70)
      - King Center, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 71)
      - Legal Guide for Lesbian and Gay Couples, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 72)
      - Liberty Hill Foundation, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 73)
      - Logo/Design, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 74)
      - Louisiana, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 75)
      - National Coming Out Project (NCOP), 1999 (Box 98, Folder 76)
      - Exxon Mobil, 1999-2002 (Box 98, Folder 77)
      - American Charities, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 78)
      - American College Personnel Association, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 79)
      - America OnLine, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 80)
      - Audit 2000 (Box 98, Folder 81)
      - Bay Windows, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 82)
      - Election 2000 (Box 98, Folder 83)
      - Israel Gays, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 84)
      - James Byrd, Jr. Foundation, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 85)
      - Leadership Washington, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 86)
      - Maclean's: Canada's Weekly Newsmagazine, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 87)
      - MTV, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 88)
      - National Coalition of Anti-Violence Programs, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 89)
      - National Coming Out Day, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 90)
      - American Red Cross, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 91)
      - B'nai Brith, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 92)
      - Legal Research Memos: Gender Identity, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 93)
      - LGBTST People of Color Org., 2001 (Box 98, Folder 94)
      - Navy: Pietropaoli HR, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 95)
      - E. Birch Files, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 96)
      - LCCR- Humphrey Awards, May 8th, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 97)
      - Diversity Initiative, 2003 (Box 98, Folder 97)
      - Vic Basile: Washington, D.C., 1986-1996 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Chastity Bono, 1996-1997 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Coming Out: Gene Hunt, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Mitchell Gold, no date (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Goldman, Rohn, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - The Rev. Peter Gomes, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Letitia Gomez, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Stephanie Gonzales, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Marc Goodman, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - Dr. Martin Gorbien, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - Rich Gordan, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - Jim Gordon, Ph.D., 1997-1998 (Box 100, Folder 12)
      - Al Gore, 1998-2000 (Box 100, Folder 13)
      - V.P. Gore, 1998-2000 (Box 100, Folder 14)
      - Gore 2000, 1995-2000 (Box 100, Folder 15)
      - Tipper Gore, 2000-2001 (Box 100, Folder 16)
      - Michael Gorges: Washington, D.C., 1997 (Box 100, Folder 17)
      - Ashley Goss, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 18)
      - Christopher Gould, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 19)
      - Ed Gould, Encino, CA, 1995-1996 (Box 100, Folder 20)
      - Jim Graham, 1996-1998 (Box 100, Folder 21)
      - Gary Grant: Texas, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 22)
      - Michael Grantham, 1997-1998 (Box 100, Folder 23)
      - Steve Grate, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 24)
      - James Gray, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 25)
      - Suzy Gray, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 26)
      - Anthony Green, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 27)
      - Bruce Greenberg: Arlington, VA, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 28)
      - Greer, Lynn, no date (Box 100, Folder 29)
      - Stephanie Grey, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 30)
      - Jackie Grover, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 31)
      - Beth A. Grupp- Vote Now '96, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 32)
      - Patrick Guerriero, no date (Box 100, Folder 33)
      - Guffey, E./Hammell, N., 1998 (Box 100, Folder 34)
      - Steve Gunderson, 1998-2000 (Box 100, Folder 35)
      - Stacey Gurian-Sherman, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 36)
      - Gutierrez Fernando, 1994-1995 (Box 100, Folder 37)
      - Mike Haase, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 38)
      - Fred C. Haeberlein, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 39)
      - Boze Hadleigh, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 40)
      - George Hadleigh, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 41)
      - Scott Hafner, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 42)
      - Hairston, Veronica, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 43)
      - Gail Halava, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 44)
      - Sandy Hale: PRIDE (Montana), 1997 (Box 100, Folder 45)
      - Carolyn Hall, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 46)
      - Gene Hall, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 47)
      - Simon Halls, no date (Box 100, Folder 48)
      - Everett Hamilton, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 49)
      - Robert Hamilton, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 50)
      - Sara Hamlen, 2003-2004 (Box 100, Folder 51)
      - Herb Hamsher: Part 1, 1997-1998 (Box 100, Folder 52)
      - Herb Hamsher: Part 2, 1998-1999 (Box 100, Folder 53)
      - Ryan Hanson, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 54)
      - Harbeck, Karen, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 55)
      - Edwin A. Hardy, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 56)
      - Marguerite Delaney Hark, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 57)
      - Senator Tom Harkin, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 58)
      - Jan Harmon, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 59)
      - Jane Harmon, 2001 (Box 100, Folder 60)
      - Rep. Jane Harmon, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 61)
      - Krista Harms: Ohumwa, IA, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 62)
      - James Harris, Ph.D., 1997 (Box 100, Folder 63)
      - Janice Alyene Harris, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 64)
      - Rand Harris: Chicago, IL, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 65)
      - Virginia Harris, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 66)
      - Scott Harshbarger- Attorney: General Massachusetts, 1995-1998 (Box 100, Folder 67)
      - Peter Hart, no date (Box 100, Folder 68)
      - Shannon Hart: Los Angeles, CA, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 69)
      - John W. Hartman, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 70)
      - Dave Harvey, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 71)
      - John Hassell, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 72)
      - George Hawkins, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 73)
      - Russ and Helma Hawkins: Kansas City, MO, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 74)
      - Dan Hazard/OUT, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 75)
      - Laurette Healey, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 76)
      - David Hebner, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 77)
      - H. Tappan Heher (Documentary Filmmaker), 1996 (Box 100, Folder 78)
      - Alison Heintz, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 79)
      - Wendy Heistad, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 80)
      - Jesse Helms, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 81)
      - Stephen E. Herbits, 1996-1998 (Box 100, Folder 82)
      - Kelli Herd, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 83)
      - Alan Hergott, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 84)
      - Alexis Herman, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 85)
      - Lynne Hermle, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 86)
      - Christine Hershey, 1999-2000 (Box 100, Folder 87)
      - Frederick Hertz, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 88)
      - Jeanne Heschele, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 89)
      - Emily Hewitt, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 90)
      - Adrienne Hickey, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 91)
      - Michael Hickey: Hollywood, CA, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 92)
      - Higinbotham, Arthur, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 93)
      - Steve Hildebrand, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 94)
      - Rick Hill- NC Dinner, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 95)
      - Hines, Thomas Ann, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 96)
      - Cynthia Ho, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 97)
      - Hochberg, Fred, 1998-2000 (Box 100, Folder 98)
      - Paul Hokemeyer, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 99)
      - Eleanor Holmes-Norton: Washington, D.C., 1996-1998 (Box 100, Folder 100)
      - Brian Holt, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 101)
      - Dr. Winston Holt, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 102)
      - Ray Hom, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 103)
      - Steve Horn, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 104)
      - Terry M. House, M.D., 1996 (Box 100, Folder 105)
      - Janet Howard, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 106)
      - Howell, Wendy, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 107)
      - Patrick M. Hudak, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 108)
      - Denay Hudson, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 109)
      - Mary Jo Hudson, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 110)
      - Mike Huffington, 1998-2003 (Box 100, Folder 111)
      - Bill Huggins, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 112)
      - Hubert H. Humphrey, III, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 113)
      - Kenneth Hurd, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 114)
      - Red Hurd, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 115)
      - Lisa Hutchins, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 116)
      - Gail Ifshin, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 117)
      - Robert Iger/ ABC Group, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 118)
      - Greg Irwin, no date (Box 100, Folder 119)
      - Amy Isaacs- ADA, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 120)
      - Jesse L. Jackson, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 121)
      - Shaun Jackson: Burtonsville, MD, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 122)
      - Richard Jacobs, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 123)
      - Greg Jakubowicz, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 124)
      - Jeffrey M. Janis, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 125)
      - Bruce W. Jaster, 2001 (Box 100, Folder 126)
      - Lorri Jean, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 127)
      - Everett Jennings, III, 1995-1999 (Box 100, Folder 128)
      - Kevin Jennings, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 129)
      - Andrea Johnson/Shorr and Ass., 1996 (Box 100, Folder 130)
      - Earvin "Magic" Johnson, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 131)
      - Janet Johnson: Clearwater, FL, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 132)
      - Johnson, Leonard Earl, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 133)
      - Linda Johnson: Milford, NH, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 134)
      - Mark F. Johnson, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 135)
      - Paul Johnson, M.D., 1996 (Box 100, Folder 136)
      - Sky Johnson, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 137)
      - Thomas C. Johnson, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 138)
      - Tom J. Johnson/ A. Timothy Nodes, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 139)
      - Beverly Jones, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 140)
      - Dr. Jones, Richard, 2001 (Box 100, Folder 141)
      - Joyner, Dwight, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 142)
      - Kalamar Design, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 143)
      - Michele Kammerer, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 144)
      - Tony Kannanthanam, no date (Box 100, Folder 145)
      - Arthur M. Kaplan, 1996-2001 (Box 100, Folder 146)
      - Elaine Kaplan, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 147)
      - Sam Kaplan, 2001 (Box 100, Folder 148)
      - Kaplan, Woody, 2001 (Box 100, Folder 149)
      - Karen Kaplowitz, 1996-1998 (Box 100, Folder 150)
      - Lynn Kappelman, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 151)
      - Lisa Karle, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 152)
      - Sonia Katyal, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 153)
      - Karen Ellen Kavey, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 154)
      - Marla Kaye, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 155)
      - Keller, David, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 156)
      - Nancy Kelly, no date (Box 100, Folder 157)
      - Sue W. Kelly, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 158)
      - Kathryn Dean Kendell, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 159)
      - Sen. Edward M. Kennedy, 1995-1998 (Box 100, Folder 160)
      - Patrick Kennedy, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 161)
      - Sen. J. Robert Kerrey, 1996-2001 (Box 100, Folder 162)
      - Senator John Kerry, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 163)
      - Killian, Brian, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 164)
      - Kinder, Lydenberg, Domini, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 165)
      - King, Billie Jean, 2001 (Box 100, Folder 166)
      - Coretta Scott King, 1996-1997 (Box 100, Folder 167)
      - Herb King, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 168)
      - Wesley King: Dayton, Ohio, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 169)
      - David Wood Kinnard, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 170)
      - Ted Kirby, 1997-1998 (Box 100, Folder 171)
      - Bill Kirkner, 1995-1996 (Box 100, Folder 172)
      - Dale and Carol Kirkpatrick, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 173)
      - Klainberg, Lesli, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 174)
      - Michelle Knapik, no date (Box 100, Folder 175)
      - Alex Knight, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 176)
      - Harry Knox: Georgia Equality Project, 2001 (Box 100, Folder 177)
      - Randy Komisar, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 178)
      - Geoffrey Kors, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 179)
      - Larry Kramer, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 180)
      - Torrie Kranz- New Orleans Dinner, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 181)
      - Tamara Kreinin, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 182)
      - Kriesil, Christin, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 183)
      - Mathilde Krim, Ph. D., 1996-1998 (Box 100, Folder 184)
      - Project Manual, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 185)
      - PUD 1: Planned Unit Development, 2000-2001 (Box 100, Folder 186)
      - PUD 2: Planned Unit Development, 2000-2001 (Box 100, Folder 187)
      - Regarding the Human Rights Campaign Real Estate Options, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 188)
      - Zoning Commission Application, 2001 (Box 100, Folder 189)
      - Los Angeles Board Leadership Meeting, September 2002 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Atlanta Pride Capital Campaign, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - Equality Rocks, 1999-2000 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - Equality Rocks VH1, 2000 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Vermont Freedom to Marry Task Force, 1999-2000 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - Wotapalava, 2001 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - Election 2000, 1995-2000 (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - Directors Meeting, January 16, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Family Pride Coalition, 1999-2002 (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - National Policy Roundtable, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - Minneapolis Dinner, September 13-15, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 11)
      - Foreign Service Exam, 2002-2003 (Box 103, Folder 12)
      - New York City Bar Association, 2001 (Box 103, Folder 13)
      - Scheduled Events, 1999-2003 (Box 103, Folder 14)
      - Thank Yous, 2000 (Box 103, Folder 15)
      - General Correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 103, Folder 16)
      - Capital Campaign, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 17)
      - September 11th Victims Fund, 2001-2002 (Box 103, Folder 18)
      - ENDA Outreach, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 19)
      - Schedule "No"s, 2000-2001 (Box 103, Folder 20)
      - HRC Financial Statements, 2001-2002 (Box 103, Folder 21)
      - Davis and Harman Meeting, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 22)
      - Equality Rocks Media, 2000 (Box 103, Folder 23)
      - Platform Committee - Democratic National Convention, 2000 (Box 103, Folder 24)
      - Michigan Events and News, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 25)
      - Columbus "Building Equality" Event 2002 (Box 103, Folder 26)
      - Hawaii - Interview and Speech, June 2002 (Box 103, Folder 27)
      - San Francisco Events and Meetings 2002 (Box 103, Folder 28)
      - Oregon and Washington, 2000 (Box 103, Folder 29)
      - Dallas Events, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 30)
      - Mike Berman Events, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 31)
      - Miscellaneous Appointments and Correspondence, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 32)
      - Philadelphia Dinner 2003, March 2003 (Box 103, Folder 33)
      - Los Angeles Dinner 2003, February 2003 (Box 103, Folder 34)
      - Memos and HRC Procedures and Outreach, 2000-2002 (Box 103, Folder 35)
      - Miscellaneous Materials, 2000 (Box 103, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 103, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, January-May 1996 (Box 103, Folder 39)
      - Correspondence, June-July 1996 (Box 103, Folder 40)
      - Correspondence, August-December 1996 (Box 103, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence, January-May 1997 (Box 103, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence, June-December 1997 (Box 103, Folder 43)
      - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 44)
      - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 45)
      - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 103, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 103, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 48)
      - HRC- Work Net, no date (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - Public Policy, 1991-1998 (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - Christian Coalition- 9/95, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - E. Birch Speech Drafts (1), 1995-1998 (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Electoral Targets, Speeches, and Statistics, 1995-1998 (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - E. Birch Speech Drafts (2), 1995-2000 (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - EB on MacNeil Lehrer, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - North Carolina Dinner, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 8)
      - North Carolina Campaign, 1996-1997 (Box 104, Folder 9)
      - E. Birch Speech Drafts (3), 1996-1998 (Box 104, Folder 10)
      - OutVote '96 Dinner, 1996-1998 (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - NCOD, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 12)
      - North Carolina Dinner 1997 (Box 104, Folder 13)
      - Retirement, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 14)
      - Angels in America, 1997-1998 (Box 104, Folder 15)
      - North Carolina, 1997-1998 (Box 104, Folder 16)
      - Speech Info, 1997-2000 (Box 104, Folder 17)
      - Board of Directors and 1998 Campaign Activities (Box 104, Folder 18)
      - News Releases, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 19)
      - North Carolina Dinner- 2/14- 2/15, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 20)
      - Speeches (1), 1998 (Box 104, Folder 21)
      - Georgia, 1998-1999 (Box 104, Folder 22)
      - Political (1), 1998-1999 (Box 104, Folder 23)
      - Political (2), 1998-1999 (Box 104, Folder 24)
      - Speeches (2), 1998-1999 (Box 104, Folder 25)
      - Atlanta 10/14, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 26)
      - Democratic Convention Speech, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 27)
      - Stanford, 2000 (Box 104, Folder 28)
      - AJ Austin- Short Speech, no date (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Business Speech, no date (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Dallabrida and Associates, no date (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Elton John AIDS Foundation, no date (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Generic Talking Points, no date (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Houston, no date (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Speech- Divide and Conquer- Buchanan, no date (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Boston, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - Dallas, Texas, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - HRC Powerpoint, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 10)
      - Los Angeles, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 11)
      - Minneapolis- St. Paul, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 12)
      - San Francisco Dinner- 12/95, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 13)
      - South Carolina- 9/95, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 14)
      - Ten City Tour, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 15)
      - Ten-Day Tour, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 16)
      - Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 105, Folder 17)
      - Chicago Black Tie Speech, 1995-1996 (Box 105, Folder 18)
      - Atlanta, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 19)
      - Columbus, Ohio- 6/96, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 20)
      - Democratic National Committee- 1996 Leadership Conference (Box 105, Folder 21)
      - Don McCleary Tribute, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 22)
      - Los Angeles- 2/96, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 23)
      - Minnesota Dinner, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 24)
      - Nashville- 1/96, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 25)
      - Nashville Dinner, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 26)
      - New Orleans, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 27)
      - North Carolina- 2/96, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 28)
      - NY Trip- 8/20, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 29)
      - Speech- Notre Dame, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 30)
      - Denver, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 31)
      - Denver Dinner- 2/97, 1996 (Box 105, Folder 32)
      - E. Birch Speech Drafts, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 33)
      - Ellen, ENDA, and Equal Rights: National Press Club 4/16/97, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 34)
      - HRC Directors' Meeting, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 35)
      - HRC Georgia Equality Project, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 36)
      - Law Review Article on ENDA, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 37)
      - Los Angeles, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 38)
      - Los Angeles Dinner, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 39)
      - Nashville Dinner, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 40)
      - National Dinner, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 41)
      - Nashville Dinner, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 42)
      - Amnesty International, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 43)
      - Boston, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 44)
      - Boston- 6/21 to 6/24, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 45)
      - Boston Debate, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 46)
      - Charlottesville/ UVA- 9/28, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 47)
      - Denver, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 48)
      - Denver: Capital Campaign- 10/25- 10/27, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 49)
      - Detroit- July 29, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 50)
      - Florida, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 51)
      - Gore Roll Out- Phil. 10/2, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 52)
      - Houston MD- 9/2000 (Box 105, Folder 53)
      - Laguna/Dallas, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 54)
      - LA Trip, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 55)
      - Los Angeles- Democratic National Convention- 8/11- 8/16, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 56)
      - Miami- 1/13, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 57)
      - NCOD- Philly, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 58)
      - Newport, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 59)
      - New York MD, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 60)
      - NGLFT Policy Roundtable- September, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 61)
      - NYC Board Meeting, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 62)
      - San Francisco Dinner- July 8, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 63)
      - United Jewish Communities- 3/20, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 64)
      - American Forum, 2000-2001 (Box 105, Folder 65)
      - Anti-Nadar Tour, 2000-2001 (Box 105, Folder 66)
      - Denver- June 14-15, 2000-2001 (Box 105, Folder 67)
      - DOT- June, 2000-2001 (Box 105, Folder 68)
      - Philadelphia MD Dinner- January 18, 2000-2001 (Box 105, Folder 69)
      - Boston MD Brunch- 1/28/01, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 70)
      - Chicago MD- 2/13/01, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 71)
      - Cleveland Dinner- May 5, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 72)
      - Columbus- May 24, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 73)
      - Denver Dinner- 2/24/01, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 74)
      - ED Retreat- Laguna Beach, CA- April 19-22, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 75)
      - LA Dinner/ Real Estate- Feb. 16-17, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 76)
      - Los Angeles- May 21, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 77)
      - Miami, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 78)
      - New York: AOL- Time Warner, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 79)
      - North Carolina M.D.- January 30-31, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 80)
      - San Francisco Dinner- June 22-24, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 81)
      - Springfield/Boston- April 30- May 1, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 82)
      - Tennessee Dinner- 3/24, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 83)
      - Elizabeth Birch- Colorado CC Event, November 14, 2002 (Box 105, Folder 84)
      - Strom Thurmond, 1990-2001 (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Wellstone, Paul, 1991-2002 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - Gramm, Phil, 1992-2002 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Vermont, 1994-2000 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Helms, Jesse, 1996-2001 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Rev. F. Jay Deacon, 1997 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - E. Birch Correspondence, 1997-2000 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Thompson, Fred, 1997-2002 (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - Torricelli, Robert, 1997-2002 (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - Dadey, Dick, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Houston Contacts, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 11)
      - Donner, Rachel, 1998-1999 (Box 106, Folder 12)
      - Cleland, Max, 1998-2002 (Box 106, Folder 13)
      - Breslauer, Mary, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 14)
      - Coburn, Heather, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 16)
      - E. Birch Correspondence (1), 1999 (Box 106, Folder 17)
      - E. Birch Correspondence (2), 1999 (Box 106, Folder 18)
      - E. Birch Correspondence (3), 1999 (Box 106, Folder 19)
      - E. Birch Correspondence (4), 1999 (Box 106, Folder 20)
      - FEC, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 21)
      - Feinstein, Michael, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 22)
      - Gray Davis, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 23)
      - Greystone, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 24)
      - HRC Staff Handbook, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 25)
      - Latham, Liz, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 26)
      - McCutchen, Doyle, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 27)
      - Shepard, Judy, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 28)
      - San Francisco- 11/17-18, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 29)
      - Seattle- 11/18-20, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 30)
      - Sen Torricelli Book, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 31)
      - Thank You Cards- E. Birch, 1999 (Box 106, Folder 32)
      - Iowa- Campaign 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 106, Folder 33)
      - Presidential, 1999-2000 (Box 106, Folder 34)
      - Roundtable- 3/16, 1999-2000 (Box 106, Folder 35)
      - New York Event, 1999-2002 (Box 106, Folder 36)
      - Democratic National Convention, 2000 (Box 106, Folder 37)
      - EQR on VH1, 2000 (Box 106, Folder 38)